http://www.cfa.vic.gov.au/privacy/

Navigation
Skip to Content
Restrictions are in place to help slow the spread of coronavirus (COVID-19) and save lives. For more information visit the DHHS website.   ×
Emergency Broadcasters
Traffic Management Points (road closures)
Traffic Management Point (road closures) FAQs
Total Fire Bans and ratings
About Fire Danger Ratings
Can I or Can’t I?
Plan & Prepare
Am I at risk?
Web Content Tile
Protecting your privacy and your personal information is an important aspect of the way CFA creates, organises and implements our activities on-line and off-line. Our collection, use and disclosure of personal information follows the requirements of the Privacy & Data Protection Act 2014.
You can access our website home page and browse our site without disclosing personal information. CFA's website does not collect or record personal information, other than information you may choose to provide to us via email.
We will only use personal information provided by you for the purposes for which it was collected. If you have emailed us, CFA staff will use contact information collected via your email to respond to your request. Any contact information provided in your email will not be added to a mailing list without your consent.
Further, any personal details within the contents of your email will only be used specifically to answer your query or respond to your comments. For example, if you provide us with your residential address so that we can provide local fire safety information, your residential address will only be used to answer your immediate query and will not be stored or used for any other purpose.
We will not disclose your personal information without your consent unless disclosure is required or sanctioned by law.
You are entitled to gain access to and/or correct any information that CFA has collected about you at any time.
Privacy Queries
If you have any queries relating to CFA's Privacy Policy, please contact the Privacy Officer at privacy@cfa.vic.gov.au or contact CFA Headquarters on 03 9262 8444.
Technical Information
This site uses 'cookies'. A cookie is a block of data that is shared between a web server and a user's browser. Cookies give the server information about a user's identity, preferences or past behaviour.
The following non-personal information (i.e. clickstream data) is automatically recorded by this site's web server for statistical and system administration purposes only:
Your server address
Your country
Your top level domain name (e.g. .com, .au, .gov)
The date and the time of your visit to the site
The pages you accessed and downloaded
The address of the last site you visited
Your operating system
The type of browser you are using
Your screen resolution
Internal search behaviour.
To the extent that this data could make you identifiable, CFA will not attempt to identify individuals from the records the server automatically generates unless that is necessary to investigate a breach of law or regulation.
We have implemented technology and security policies, rules and measures to protect the personal information that we have under our control from: unauthorised access, improper use, alteration, unlawful or accidental destruction and accidental loss. We will remove personal information from our system where it is no longer required (except where archiving is required).
Use of Victorian Electoral Commission information for mailouts
To facilitate a mailout to provide information about fire preparedness, the Victorian Electoral Commissioner has permitted the use of the names and addresses of Victorian electors (excluding silent electors and overseas electors) in accordance with section 34 of the Electoral Act 2002. Enrolment information was not provided to CFA, and remained in the control of the Victorian Electoral Commission at all times.
Please call on 1800 068 611 or email communityprograms@cfa.vic.gov.au if you have any queries regarding the usage of enrolment data.
